Guide to the Les K. Wright papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010.
Wright, Les K. papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010
- Series VI. Audiovisual and Computer Media
  - Raw footage for 1993 Bear documentary., [8mm videotape]; John Topping
    - Hank Becker-DC; Confederate Bears-North Carolina (Box 31)
Classic Bear. Issues 1-2 (1996-1997)
Daddy Bear. 1994:Jan.,Apr./May-June/July,Sept./Oct.; 1995:Feb.,Apr./May; v.2:no.3-6 (1995:June/July-Dec./Jan.); v.3:no.1-2 (1996:Feb./Mar.-[Apr./May])
Das Graphische werk von the graphic work of Lovis Corinth. By Karl Schwarz. (1985)
Der Barenkult Das Tier im Mann!. By Rainer Horman und Jim Baker (Hrsg.). (2004)
Digital Photographer August 2001 (John Rand featured on pages 86-89)
Digital Photographer November 2002 (John Rand featured on pages 66-70)
Digital Photographer November 2003 (John Rand featured on pages 86-89)
Encyclopedia of Homosexuality.vol 1, vol 2 By Wayne R.Dynes. (1990)
European Journal of Cultural studies. v.1:no 1 (January 1998)
Faeries Bears and Leathermen. By Peter Hennen. (2008)
Gay and Lesbian Biography. By Michael J. Tyrkus. (1997)
Gay Histories and Cultures. By George E. Haggerty. (2000)
Gay men write about hometowns where they belong. By John Preston. (1991)
Getting it on online:Cyberspace, Gay Male Sexuality and Emboided Identity. By John Edward Campbell. (2004)
Heavy Duty. Issue 8-10 (1998)
Husky. v.1:no.1,3 (1991); v.3:no.3 (1996)
Journal of Homosexuality. Vol 46,no 1/2. (2003)
Köln & Düsselsorf von hinten: Lese- und Reisebuch für Schwule, Gays und anderen Freunde. Edited by Michael Zgonjanin. (1985)
Loving Mountains, Loving Men. By Jeff Mann. (2005)
More Bear Cookin'. PJ Gray. (2005)
Moving On. By Dann Hazel. (1999)
Mud Mania magazine. Rio Nido, California.
Now UK No. 16 March 2000
One Thousand Beards, A cultural History of Facial Hair. By Allan Peterkin. (2001)
Out in the workplace. By Richard A.Rasi, D.Min. Lourdes Rodriguez-Nogues, Ed.d. (1995)
Pinups no. 5 (2008:March)
Queering the canon. By Christoph Lorey, John L.Plews. (1998)
Queer sites, gay urban histories since 1600. By David Higgs. (1999)
Serenity: challenging the fear of AIDS, from despair to hope. By Paul Reed. (1987)
Song of the Loon. By Richard Amory. (1966)
Spartacus...guide for gay men. 1995/1996 edition
Sugar Bear's Den. v.1:issue 1-4,7 (1996:Nov./Dec.-1997:May/June,1997:Nov./Dec.); v.2 (1996); v.3:issue 2-5 (1999:Mar./Apr.-Nov./Dec.); v.4:issue 1-2 (2000:Jan./Feb.-May/June)
Syphilis as AIDS. By Robert Ben Mitchell. (1990)
Tales from the Bear Cult. By Mark Hemry. (2001)
The Bear and his sons. By James M. Taggart. (1997)
The Bear Book. By Les Wright. (1997)
The Bear Book II. By Les Wright. (2001)
The Bear Handbook. By Ray Kampf. (2000)
The Butch manual. By Clark Henley. (1982)
The Leatherman's Handbook. By Larry Towsend. (1972)
The Naked Bear. By John Bierhorst. (1987)
The Sacred Paw. By Paul Shepard, Barrry Sanders. (1985)
You don't have to die: unraveling the AIDS myth. By Leon Chaitow. (1994)
Young and hairy. By David Butt. (1999)